Florence Hollis and Rosemary Ross Reynolds Papers, 1863-1987
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- Series V. CASE RECORDS
  - Mitchell, George and Mary; Cleveland FS, 1936, undated (Box 28, Folder 197)
  - Mobley, Harry and Lois; Columbia University School of Social Work, ca. 1969 (Box 28, Folder 198)
  - Moore; Family Service Association of America, 1960, undated (Box 28, Folder 199)
  - Morgan, Edward and Jessie; School of Applied Social Sciences, Western Reserve University, 1939, undated (Box 28, Folder 200)
  - Morton, George and Evelyn; 1960 (Box 28, Folder 201)
  - Mueller, William and Carol; New York School of Social Work, CW 1, course #120, 1944-1952, undated (Box 28, Folder 202)
  - Mulholland, Michael and Florence; Philadelphia Study of Marriage Counseling, 1942, undated (Box 28, Folder 203)
  - Mundi, John and Teresa; School of Applied Social Sciences, Western Reserve University, 1936, undated (Box 28, Folder 204)
  - Murray, John and Genevieve; Philadelphia FS, 1931, undated (Box 28, Folder 205)
  - Murray, Joseph and Elizabeth; CCRA, 1934-1935 (Box 28, Folder 206)
  - N. case (Nelson); New York School of Social Work, 1952-1956, undated (Box 28, Folder 207)
  - N., Mr.; New York School of Social Work, undated (Box 29, Folder 208)
  - N., Mrs. (Rose); New York School of Social Work, course #220, 1951-1952, undated (Box 29, Folder 209)
  - Nagy, Mrs.; School of Applied Social Sciences, Western Reserve University, 1937, undated (Box 29, Folder 210)
  - Nathan, Anthony and Lois; New York School of Social Work, course #124, 1950, undated (Box 29, Folder 211)
  - Nathanson; New York School of Social Work, CW 3, 1949-1956, undated (Box 29, Folder 212)
  - Newman; New York School of Social Work, 1952-1953, undated (Box 29, Folder 213)
  - Newton (Norales), John and Rose; New York School of Social Work, CW 2, course #122, 1945, undated (Box 29, Folder 214)
  - Nichols; New York School of Social Work, CW 2, course #121 [?] and #122 [?], 1949-1953 (Box 29, Folder 215)
  - Niehardt; undated (Box 29, Folder 216)
  - O., Mrs. (Margaret); New York School of Social Work, 1949-1951, undated (Box 29, Folder 217)
  - O., Sally; New York School of Social Work, 1951-1952 (Box 29, Folder 218)
  - O'Hara, Daniel; New York School of Social Work, CW 2, course #122, 1947-1960, undated (Box 29, Folder 219)
  - O'Neill, Michael; Pennsylvania School of Social Work, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 220)
  - Orton, James and Frances; New York School of Social Work, 1941-1943, undated (Box 29, Folder 221)
  - Ottero; Columbia University School of Social Work, 1965-1968, undated (Box 29, Folder 222)
  - Owens; Columbia University School of Social Work, 1965-1968, undated (Box 29, Folder 223)
  - Parker, Ruth; New York School of Social Work, course #124, 1949-1952, undated (Box 29, Folder 224)
  - Paul, William and Margaret; New York School of Social Work, CW 3, course #123, 1943-1954, undated (Box 29, Folder 225)
  - Pavia; Cleveland Study of Marriage Counseling, ca. 1940 (Box 29, Folder 226)
  - Peters, Arthur; Columbia University School of Social Work, 1967-1969, undated (Box 29, Folder 227)
  - Peters, Harry; 1963-1964, undated (Box 29, Folder 228)
  - Peters, Thomas and Marian; New York School of Social Work, course #124, 1950-1951, undated (Box 29, Folder 229)
  - Pietro, Pat and Jewel; Cleveland Study of Marriage Counseling, 1940, undated (Box 29, Folder 230)
  - Pollack, Sarah; New York School of Social Work, undated (Box 29, Folder 231)
  - Popinoe, John and Agnes; 1935-1936, undated (Box 29, Folder 232)
  - Porter, Alfred and Teresa; School of Applied Social Sciences, Western Reserve University, CW 1, 1933, undated (Box 29, Folder 233)
  - Poverty Cases; 1963-1965, 1985, undated (Box 29, Folder 234)
  - Pratt, Mary; New York School of Social Work, 1950, undated (Box 30, Folder 235)
  - Preston, Henry and Janet; School of Applied Social Sciences, Western Reserve University, undated (Box 30, Folder 236)
  - Price, Charles M.; New York School of Social Work, course #104, 1945-1950, undated (Box 30, Folder 237)
  - Proctor, Norman and Mildred; School of Applied Social Sciences, Western Reserve University, 1933, undated (Box 30, Folder 238)
  - Psychiatric Hospital; 1961-1962 (Box 30, Folder 239)
  - Purka, Goldie; Cleveland EDCR, 1936, undated (Box 30, Folder 240)
  - Pusey, George and Sophie; School of Applied Social Sciences, Western Reserve University, 1932-1936, undated (Box 30, Folder 241)
  - Queen, Samuel and Georgia; St. Louis Institute, 1952, undated (Box 30, Folder 242)
  - R., Mrs.; New York School of Social Work, course #121 and course #122, ca. 1961-1963 (Box 30, Folder 243)
  - Randall, Tommy; New York School of Social Work, course #220, 1957-1959, undated (Box 30, Folder 244)
  - Reger, Max and Helen; AC, Cleveland, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 245)
  - Rich; undated (Box 30, Folder 246)
  - Robinson, Stanley and Helen; 1937-1938, undated (Box 30, Folder 247)
  - Rodney, Mrs.; Columbia University School of Social Work, 1966-1968, undated (Box 30, Folder 248)
  - Rosaria; New York School of Social Work, course #121, undated (Box 30, Folder 249)
  - Rogers; 1951 (Box 31, Folder 250)
  - Rosen, Sadie and Julius; 1958, undated (Box 31, Folder 251)
  - Ross, Edward; New York School of Social Work, CW 1, course #120, 1945-1949, undated (Box 31, Folder 252)
  - Roth, Vera; Columbia University School of Social Work, undated (Box 31, Folder 253)
  - Rozek, Joseph and Mildred; Cleveland Study of Marriage Counseling, 1942, undated (Box 31, Folder 254)
  - Rucci, Alexander and Cecelia; Philadelphia Study of Marriage Counseling, 1942, undated (Box 31, Folder 255)
  - Ryman; New York School of Social Work, 1954-1964, undated (Box 31, Folder 256)
  - S., David; New York School of Social Work, 1953-1954, undated (Box 31, Folder 257)
  - S., John; New York School of Social Work, CW 4, course #123, 1951-1952, undated (Box 31, Folder 258)
  - S., Miss; New York School of Social Work, CW 2, course #122, 1939-1953, undated (Box 31, Folder 259)
  - Sacks, Dan; New York School of Social Work, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 260)
  - Saltman; 1968-1969, undated (Box 31, Folder 261)
  - Saltzman, Joseph and Erminie; CCRA, Cleveland, 1936 (Box 31, Folder 262)
  - Samuels, Robert and Alva; Family Service Association of America "exhibit record," Columbia University School of Social Work, 1965-1969, undated (Box 31, Folder 263)
  - Sanborn, George and Marian; 1944-1954, undated (Box 31, Folder 264)
  - Sanca, Pasquale and Mary; Family Service Society of America "exhibit record," 1950-1956, undated (Box 31, Folder 265)
  - Sanson, Clarence and Elizabeth; 1935, undated (Box 31, Folder 266)
  - Santos, Edwardo and Florita; Columbia University School of Social Work, 1967-1969, undated (Box 31, Folder 267)
  - Saunders, Nelson and Agnes; Philadelphia, 1933, undated (Box 31, Folder 268)
  - Saunders, Otto and Janet; CCRA, Cleveland, 1935-1936 (Box 31, Folder 269)
  - Schmidt, Mr. and Mrs.; Pennsylvania School of Social Work, Philadelphia, 1933-1935 (Box 31, Folder 270)
  - Schultz, James and Edna; 1934-1935, undated (Box 31, Folder 271)
  - Schwartz, Clara; Columbia University School of Social Work, 1961-1962, undated (Box 31, Folder 272)
  - Shaker, Emily; 1936 (Box 31, Folder 273)
  - Shimon and Reuven; New York School of Social Work, 1950-1963, undated (Box 31, Folder 274)
  - Shorghaufer; Cleveland Study on Marriage Counseling, 1939-1940, undated (Box 32, Folder 275)
  - Siders; AC, Cleveland, 1935-1936, undated (Box 32, Folder 276)
  - Simko, Raymond and Ann; AC, Cleveland, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 277)
  - Sloan; Cleveland, ca. 1937 (Box 32, Folder 278)
  - Smidenski, Frank; New York School of Social Work, 1951, undated (Box 32, Folder 279)
  - Smith; Cleveland Study of Marriage Counseling, 1939-1940, undated (Box 32, Folder 280)
  - Smith, Anne; Chattanooga Institute, 1926-1927, undated (Box 32, Folder 281)
  - Smith, Carol; Columbia University School of Social Work,1968, undated (Box 32, Folder 282)
  - Smythe, Louis and Maria; CCRA, Cleveland, 1935 (Box 32, Folder 283)
  - Sobolewski; 1960-1961 (Box 32, Folder 284)
  - Stalin, Edgar; Chattanooga and Eglesmere, 1935-1936, undated (Box 32, Folder 285)
  - Stanton, George and Mary; Eglesmere, 1935-1937, undated (Box 32, Folder 286)
  - Straus; New York School of Social Work, 1953-1964. n.d. (Box 32, Folder 287)
  - "Stringbean interviews and other observation sketches;" 1924-1937, undated (Box 32, Folder 288)
  - Stwan; Cleveland Study on Marriage Counseling, 1940, undated (Box 32, Folder 289)
  - Summer, Samuel and Bertha; New York School of Social Work,1951, undated (Box 32, Folder 290)
  - Swope; New York School of Social Work, CW 2, course #122,1939, undated (Box 32, Folder 291)
  - Sunporch Group; Boston University, School of Social Work, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 292)
  - Szwydky, Anna; 1927 (Box 32, Folder 293)
  - T., Mr.; Community Service Society of New York, 1950 (Box 32, Folder 294)
  - Thomas, George and Margaret; 1938, undated (Box 32, Folder 295)
  - Thomas, Edward and Elizabeth; 1934, undated (Box 32, Folder 296)
  - Tobin, Henry and Ellen; CCRA, Cleveland, 1934-1935, undated (Box 32, Folder 297)
  - Torino, Michael; New York School of Social Work, 1946-1948, undated (Box 32, Folder 298)
  - Torres; 1969-1970, undated (Box 32, Folder 299)
  - Torvald, Jan and Lisa; Family Service Society of America "exhibit record," 1956-1957, undated (Box 33, Folder 300)
  - Tracy, Mrs.; undated (Box 33, Folder 301)
  - Trickett, Bob; 1938, undated (Box 33, Folder 302)
  - Troka, Margaret; AC, Cleveland, 1937-1940, undated (Box 33, Folder 303)
  - Valenti; 1959, undated (Box 33, Folder 304)
  - Van Horn; Cleveland Study of Marriage Counseling, 1940, undated (Box 33, Folder 305)
  - Vargo; undated (Box 33, Folder 306)
  - Veteran; New York School of Social Work, CW 3, course #123, 1949-1950, undated (Box 33, Folder 307)
  - W. Case; 1950-1951 (Box 33, Folder 308)
  - W. Family; 1964, undated (Box 33, Folder 309)
  - Wagner, Gerald and Tilda; 1935-1936, undated (Box 33, Folder 310)
  - Wallace, Percy and Dolly; School of Applied Social Sciences, Western Reserve University, 1934-1935, undated (Box 33, Folder 311)
  - Ward; Dr. Werner's seminar, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 312)
  - Weiner; Columbia University School of Social Work, 1967, undated (Box 33, Folder 313)
  - Whistler, Katherine; CCRA, 1935-1936, undated (Box 33, Folder 314)
  - Williams, Laura; Dr. Werner's seminar, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 315)
  - Williams, William and Genevieve; 1933 (Box 33, Folder 316)
  - Wilson, Walter and Jean; New York School of Social Work, 1953-1962, undated (Box 33, Folder 317)
  - Wilmington Cases; The Family Society, Wilmington, Delaware, 1939-1940 (Box 33, Folder 318)
  - Wisner, Peter; 1946-1947, undated (Box 33, Folder 319)
  - Witte, Gustave and Clara; New York School of Social Work, CW 1, course #121, 1941-1951, undated (Box 33, Folder 320)
  - Wright, Fred and Sylvia; New York School of Social Work, course #123, 1951-1953, undated (Box 33, Folder 321)
  - X., Mrs.; Columbia University School of Social Work, ca. 1963 (Box 33, Folder 322)
  - X.X., Mr.; New York School of Social Work, course #120 and course #121, 1954-1956, undated (Box 33, Folder 323)
  - Youth Board Cases; New York School of Social Work, 1953 (Box 33, Folder 324)
  - Zalor, Janet; New York School of Social Work, 1950-1951, undated (Box 33, Folder 325)
  - Zoland, Frank and Margaret; 1943 (Box 33, Folder 326)
  - Zucker; 1966, undated (Box 33, Folder 327)
  - Index of cases, undated (Box 33, Folder 328)
  - Case records on index cards, A-Z, 1926-1971 (Box 33, Folder 329)
- Series VI. WRITING AND SPEECHES
  - Speeches and papers
    - "Notes for various speeches, 1930-1940"
      - ca. 1930-1940 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - "Why a Private Family Agency?," ca. 1930-1940 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - On supervision, ca. 1930-1940 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Cash versus kind, ca. 1930-1940 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - "Making the Most of Our Children," ca. 1930-1940 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - "Making the Most of Our Children," final version, ca. 1930-1940 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - "Private and Public Relief," ca. 1937-1939 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - On curriculum changes, ca. 1938 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - "The Caseworker and the Modern Family," and "Individualized Service to Families," 1938 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - "The Place of the Private Family Welfare Society in the Community," 1938 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Edwards family, ca. 1936-1939 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - "How can the Caseworkers Attitudes Affect Treatment," 1939 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - ca. 1935-1939, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - 1940-1943, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - 1944-1951 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - ca. 1950-1954 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - "Casework with Families Having Marital and Parent- Child Conflicts," notes, ca. 1950-1954 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - "Case Work in any Category," speech notes and program, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Papers and speeches on diagnosis in casework, 1954-1955 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Papers, reviews, and discussion, ca. 1955-1959 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - "The Nature of Personality Change in Casework," notes, paper and commmentary, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - "Analysis of Two Casework Approaches," revisions and discussion, 1956-1962, ca. 1986 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Comments on Helen Perlman's book, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Papers, reviews and speeches, 1960-1969 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - "Casework and Social Class," speech, review and related material, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Letters to the editor, 1966, ca. 1970s (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - "The Psychosocial Approach to the Practice of Casework," 1969 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - "Current and Future Trends in Social Casework," early and revised drafts, 1971-1973 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - ca. 1972-1978 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - "Growth and Synthesis in Psychosocial Casework," 1972 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Boston meeting, papers and notes, ca. 1973-1975 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Forward to Poverty and Social Casework Services, Ben Orcutt, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - "Social Casework: The Psychological Approaches," 1977 Encyclopedia of Social Work, correspondence and draft, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - "Evaluation: Clinical Results and Research Methodology," notes, ca. 1975 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - "Evaluation: Clinical Results and Research Methodology," draft and mailing list, 1976-ca. 1977 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - "On Revisiting Social Work," early draft and correspondence, ca. 1978 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - "On Revisiting Social Work," address draft and program, ca. 1978 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - "On Revisiting Social Work," commentary and correspondence, ca. 1978-1980 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Introduction and related correspondence for Clinical Social Workers as Psychotherapists, by Florence Lieberman, ca. 1979-1982 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - "For Eileen's book," 1981 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - "Clinical Social Work--What is It?", speech, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Speeches, 1982-1983 (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - "How It Really Was," drafts and related materials, ca. 1983 (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - "How It Really Was," commentary and correspondence, ca. 1983-1986 (Box 36, Folder 44)
    - "Psychological Perspective in Clinical Social Work, a Personal Perspective of How it Really Began," videocassette, Smith College, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 45)
    - "The Early Growth and Development of Modern Social Casework," notes, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - Speeches, undated (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - Discussions of Florence Hollis's papers, 1938-1960, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - Publications
    - The Journal of Social Casework (formerly The Family), issues edited by Hollis, 1942-1947 (Box 36, Folder 49)
    - Articles
      - 1931-ca. 1940, 1985, undated (Box 36, Folder 50)
      - Articles and pamphlet, 1945-1959, undated (Box 36, Folder 51)
      - Articles and publication list, 1960-ca. 1983, undated (Box 37, Folder 52)
    - Books
      - Social Case Work in Practice: Six Case Studies
        - Case notes, ca. 1930s, ca. 1976 (Box 37, Folder 53)
        - Yelenk (Homenko) case, Institute of Family Service, Cleveland, 1938, ca. 1985 (Box 37, Folder 54)
        - Reviews, 1939-1940 (Box 37, Folder 55)
        - Correspondence, 1939-1941, 1955 (Box 37, Folder 56)
      - Women in Marital Conflict
        - Correspondence, 1945-1953 (Box 37, Folder 57)
        - Reviews, 1949-1951 (Box 37, Folder 58)
      - Casework: A Psychosocial Therapy, 1st and 2nd editions
        - Notes and reviews, ca. 1964-1973 (Box 37, Folder 59)
        - Reviews from abroad, 1964-1968 (Box 37, Folder 60)
        - Correspondence concerning Japanese translation, 1965-1979, undated (Box 37, Folder 61)
      - Casework: A Psychosocial Therapy, 3rd edition
        - Introduction, acknowledgments and notes, ca. 1980 (Box 37, Folder 62)
        - Introduction, acknowledgments and epiloque, 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 63)
        - Preface, acknowledgments, and table of contents, galley proofs, ca. 1980-1981 (Box 37, Folder 64)
        - Corrected index, ca. 1981 (Box 37, Folder 65)
        - Chapter 1
          - "Scraps of 10/15 copy," ca. 1979 (Box 37, Folder 66)
          - Early draft, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 67)
          - Early draft, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 68)
          - Mary Woods' copy, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 69)
          - Intermediate draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 70)
          - "Scraps of final 1," ca. 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 71)
          - Endnotes, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 72)
          - Fragments, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 73)
        - Chapter 2
          - Notes and drafts, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 74)
          - Early draft, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 75)
          - Early draft, Mary Woods' copy, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 76)
          - Early draft, fragments, ca. 1979 (Box 38, Folder 77)
          - Intermediate draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 78)
          - Chapter 2 and 4, fragments, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 79)
        - Chapter 3
          - Early draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 80)
          - Intermediate draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 81)
          - Copy edited draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 82)
        - Chapter 4
          - Early notes, ca. 1979 (Box 38, Folder 83)
          - Early draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 84)
          - Early draft, Mary Woods' copy, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 85)
          - Early draft, fragments, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 86)
        - Chapter 5
          - Preliminary notes, ca. 1979 (Box 38, Folder 87)
          - Early draft 1, Mary Woods' copy, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 88)
          - Early draft 2, Mary Woods' copy, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 89)
          - Early draft, fragments, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 90)
          - Intermediate draft, ca. 1980 (Box 38, Folder 91)
          - "Scraps of final 5," ca. 1979-1980 (Box 38, Folder 92)
        - Chapter 6
          - Early notes, ca. 1979 (Box 38, Folder 93)
        - Chapter 7
          - Early notes, ca. 1979 (Box 38, Folder 94)
          - Early draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 95)
          - Intermediate draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 96)
          - Fragments, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 97)
        - Chapter 8
          - Early draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 98)
          - Intermediate draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 99)
          - Copy edited draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 100)
        - Chapter 9
          - Early draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 101)
          - Intermediate draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 102)
          - Copy edited draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 103)
        - Chapter 10
          - Early draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 104)
          - Intermediate draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 105)
          - Copy edited draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 106)
        - Chapter 11
          - Intermediate draft 1, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 107)
          - Intermediate draft 2, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 108)
          - Copy edited draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 109)
        - Chapter 12
          - Early draft and related material, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 110)
          - Intermediate draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 111)
          - Copy edited draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 112)
        - Chapter 13
          - Early notes and fragments, ca. 1979 (Box 40, Folder 113)
          - Early draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 114)
          - Intermediate draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 115)
        - Chapter 14
          - Early draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 116)
          - Fragments, ca. 1979 (Box 40, Folder 117)
          - Intermediate draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 118)
          - Fragments, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 119)
        - Chapter 15
          - "Chapter 14, new 15--scraps," ca. 1979 (Box 40, Folder 120)
          - Early draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 121)
          - Intermediate draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 122)
          - Fragments, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 123)
        - Chapter 16
          - "Remnants," ca. 1979 (Box 40, Folder 124)
          - Early draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 125)
          - Early draft with Mary Woods' comments, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 126)
          - Intermediate draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 127)
          - Fragments, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 128)
        - Chapter 17
          - Preliminary draft, ca. 1979 (Box 40, Folder 129)
          - Early draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 130)
          - Intermediate draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 131)
          - Odds and ends, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 132)
        - Chapter 18
          - Early draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 133)
          - Intermediate draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 134)
          - "Odds and ends," ca. 1979 (Box 41, Folder 135)
          - Fragments, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 136)
        - Chapter 19
          - Early draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 137)
          - Intermediate draft 1, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 138)
          - Intermediate draft 2, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 139)
          - Copy edited draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 140)
        - Chapter 20
          - Ideas, resource materials, and fragments, ca. 1978-1980 (Box 41, Folder 141)
          - Preliminary notes, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 142)
          - Early draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 143)
          - Early draft, Mary Woods' copy, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 144)
          - Intermediate draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 145)
          - And appendix A, later draft, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 146)
          - "Odds and ends," ca. 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 147)
          - Fragments, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 148)
        - Related materials
          - Selected end notes, ca. 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 149)
          - Ideas, reference materials and correspondence, ca. 1969-1980 (Box 41, Folder 150)
          - Conference ideas, ca. 1978-1979 (Box 41, Folder 151)
          - "Recent conference" notes, ca. 1980 (Box 42, Folder 152)
          - Manuscript review materials with correspondence, ca. 1979-1980, undated (Box 42, Folder 153)
          - Review and revision prospectus, ca. 1979 (Box 42, Folder 154)
          - Miscellaneous materials, ca. 1979, undated (Box 42, Folder 155)
          - "Book odds and ends on desk 7/30/80," ca. 1980 (Box 42, Folder 156)
          - Author's questionnaire, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 157)
          - Reviews, 1982-1986 (Box 42, Folder 158)
      - Published Books: Social Case Work in Practice: Six Case Studies, 1939; Women in Marital Conflict, 1955 (Dutch edition); and Casework, A Psychosocial Therapy (various editions, 1964- ) (Box 42)
- Series VII. TYPOLOGY RESEARCH
  - Notes and findings